(Zack:)Score.
I got an Archie,
Betty and Veronica,
and a Jughead.
(Zack:)All set
for my weekend number twos.
(Sheldon:)Congratulations.
(Sheldon:)Zack, how would you
like to be Superman?
(Zack:)I don't know, sounds like
a lot of responsibility.
(Leonard:)Fine, if Zack's going
to be Superman,
(Leonard:)I want to be
Green Lantern.
(Raj:)But I'm Green Lantern.
(Leonard:)You can be Aquaman.
(Raj:)I don't want to be Aquaman.
(Raj:)He sucks.
(Raj:)He sucks
underwater.
fish pee.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me,
(Sheldon:)I believe Aquaman uses
his telepathic powers
(Sheldon:)to request the fish do
their business elsewhere.
(Zack:)Hey, babe.
(Penny:)I'm still mad at you.
(Zack:)Well, you won't be
(Zack:)when you hear the great news.
(Penny:)What great news?
(Zack:)We're going to
a costume party
(Zack:)at the comic book store
on New Year's Eve,
(Zack:)and you get to
be Wonder Woman.